Guide to the William Manchester Papers, 1934 - 2004
William Manchester Papers1934 - 2004
- Series I: Writings, 1943-1995
  - Books
    - A Rockefeller Family Portrait, 1959
      - 1st draft (Box 186, Folder 14-16)
      - 1st draft (Box 187, Folder 1-3)
      - Draft (Box 187, Folder 4-8)
      - Misc. pages (Box 187, Folder 9)
      - Preface (Box 187, Folder 10)
      - Draft sent to the Rockefellers (Box 187, Folder 11)
      - Draft, Ch. 1 (Box 187, Folder 12-13)
      - Draft, Ch. 6 (Box 187, Folder 14-15)
      - Draft, Ch. 6 revs. (Box 187, Folder 16)
      - Draft, What Every Man May Expect of Nelson (Box 187, Folder 17)
      - Dust jacket (Box 187, Folder 18)
      - Reviews (Box 187, Folder 19)
    - Shadow of the Monsoon, 1956
      - Correspondence (Box 187, Folder 20-21)
      - Background material (Box 187, Folder 22-24)
      - Clippings (Box 187, Folder 25)
      - Notes (Box 187, Folder 26-27)
      - Notes (Box 188, Folder 1-3)
      - Clumps (Box 432)
      - 1st draft (Box 188, Folder 4-22)
      - 1st draft (Box 189, Folder 1-11)
      - Draft pages (Box 189, Folder 12-19)
      - Draft (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
      - Setting copy (Box 190, Folder 3-7)
      - Dust jacket (Box 190, Folder 8)
      - 1968 rev. (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - [1968 rev.?] (Box 191, Folder 2-12)
    - A World Lit Only By Fire, 1992
      - Correspondence & sources, 1990 Jul-1991 Sep (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - Bibliography, 1990 Nov-1991 Jun and undated (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Early partial draft (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - Magellan MS (Box 192, Folder 4-8)
      - Intermediate draft (Box 192, Folder 9-11)
      - Intermediate draft (Box 193, Folder 1-2)
      - Later draft (Box 193, Folder 3-7)
      - Setting copy (Box 193, Folder 8-11)
      - Setting copy (Box 194, Folder 1-2)
      - Marked set (Box 194, Folder 3-5)
      - Marked set, copy (Box 194, Folder 6-8)
      - Marked set, 1992 Jan 23 (Box 194, Folder 9-10)
      - Master set, 1st repro. (Box 194, Folder 11-13)
      - Second revision, repro. (Box 194, Folder 14)
      - Chronology corrections, 1992 Feb (Box 194, Folder 15)
      - Maps and fragments (Box 194, Folder 16)
  - Other writings
    - An Act of Conscience, 1968 (Box 195, Folder 1-3)
    - Almanac of World War I introduction, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Anatomy of a Novelist, circa 1961 (Box 195, Folder 5-7)
    - Anthony Eden book review, 1986 (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - The Berkshire Hills, 1960 (Box 195, Folder 9-12)
    - Best Friend of Springfiel, 1956 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - The Big Spender, 1950s (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - The Biggest Con Man in the Marines, 1995 (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - Bobby, 1988 (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - Boffo War, 1980s-90s (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - The Byrd Machine, 1952 (Box 195, Folder 18-19)
    - The Case of Luella Mundell, 1951-52 (Box 195, Folder 20-22)
    - The Case of Luella Mundell, 1951-52 (Box 196, Folder 1-10)
    - Chronicle of Twentieth Century Conflict foreward, 1992 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - The Connecticut, 1980s (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Covering the Stevenson Charm, 1975 (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - Dark Mirror, 1950s (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - The Department of the Treasury, 1961 (Box 196, Folder 15-19)
    - 'Din! George P. Din!', undated (Box 196, Folder 20)
    - The Disappearance, undated (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - Dope-The Assassin of Youth, 1950s (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - Dr. Johnson clumps, 1950s (Box 366)
    - Education a Panacea?, 1955 (Box 196, Folder 23)
    - Eqypt, 1950s (Box 196, Folder 24)
    - Either/Or, 1950s (Box 196, Folder 25)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica article on Krupp family, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 26)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica article on Kennedy family, 1972 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica article on Kennedys, 1977 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Epitaph How We Would Be Remembered, circa 1980s (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - The Evil That Men Do, 1950s (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Family Hero, 1950s (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Fast Time, 1955 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - The Fateful Lightning, 1955-56
      - Correspondence (Box 197, Folder 7)
      - Code key (Box 197, Folder 8)
      - Outlines (Box 197, Folder 9)
      - Plotting (Box 197, Folder 10)
      - Working file (Box 197, Folder 11)
      - Maps (Box 197, Folder 12)
      - Historical materials (Box 197, Folder 13)
      - Notebook (Box 197, Folder 14)
      - Clumps (Box 380-381)
      - 1st draft (Box 197, Folder 15-22)
      - Revs. (Box 197, Folder 23)
      - Fair copy (Box 198, Folder 1-2)
      - Draft (Box 198, Folder 3-7)
    - The First World War, 1962 (Box 198, Folder 8-11)
    - The Founding Grandfather, 1974 (Box 198, Folder 12-14)
    - The Fringes of Power: 10 Downing Steet Diaries book review, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - The Great Bank Holiday, 1957 (Box 198, Folder 16-17)
    - The Great Bank Holiday, 1957 (Box 199, Folder 1-3)
    - The Great Vivisection Dog Fight, 1950 (Box 199, Folder 4-5)
    - 'The Happiest Years I Have Ever Known', 1995 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Hard News, 1950s (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - How the Movies Chased the Blues Away in the Last Depression, 1975 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - I Do Not Like Thee Ravished, Mother Goose, 1950s (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Ideas, undated (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - In Defense of Snobs, 1957 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Inside the Third Reich book review, 1970 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Intellectual: Post-War Model, 1946-47 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Into the Sewer Pipe, 1951 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Leadership, 1980s-90s (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Life Along the Connecticut, 1960-62 (Box 199, Folder 16-25)
    - The Life and Times of a Slumlord, 1955 (Box 199, Folder 26)
    - Lower the Star-Spangled Banner, 1974 (Box 199, Folder 27)
    - Louisville, 1950s (Box 199, Folder 28)
    - Louiseville: Belle of Kentucky, 1956 (Box 199, Folder 29)
    - Louisville Cashes in on Culture, 1955 (Box 199, Folder 30-31)
    - Man of Property, 1955 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Maryland's Historic Capital, 1956 (Box 200, Folder 2-5)
    - Mencken obituary, 1950s (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Money, Bears, and Bulls, 1962-63 (Box 200, Folder 7-12)
    - Mother Goose Uncensored, 1950s (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Murder Tour of New England, 1962 (Box 200, Folder 14-16)
    - Our Embassy in Paris, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 17-19)
    - Our War in the Pacific, 1959 (Box 201, Folder 1-3)
    - Out in the Crazy All Alone, 1950s (Box 201, Folder 4-7)
    - Pasajes, 1954 (Box 201, Folder 8-12)
    - The Poison Ivy League, 1950s (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - The Pumpkin Papers in the Transcripts, 1974 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - The Pursuit of Happiness, and Other Sobering Thoughts, 1978 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Reds, 1953 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Remembrance, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 17-20)
    - Saturday Evening Post serial, 1956 (Box 201, Folder 21-23)
    - The Shrinking Republican Majority, 1974 (Box 202, Folder 1-3)
    - A Silent Sound Track in Dallas, 1993
      - Correspondence (Box 202, Folder 4)
      - Research (Box 202, Folder 5-7)
      - Loose pages (Box 202, Folder 8)
      - November 22, 1963: The Chain of Evidence in Dallas, 1991-92 (Box 202, Folder 9-11)
      - Chain of Evidence: Dallas, 1963, 1991-92 (Box 202, Folder 12)
      - Trial by Biography (Box 202, Folder 13)
      - Death and Accoustics in Dallas, 1993 (Box 202, Folder 14)
      - Death and Accoustics in Dallas alt. ver., 1993 (Box 202, Folder 15)
      - A Silent Soundtrack in Dallas, 1993 (Box 202, Folder 16)
      - An Old, Silent Soundtrack in Dallas, 1993 (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - The Spanish-American War, 1961 (Box 203, Folder 1-3)
    - The Style is the (Changing) Woman, 1970s (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - The Takers, 1955 (Box 203, Folder 5-19)
    - The Taxpayer, undated (Box 203, Folder 20)
    - That's Our Weakness Now, 1950s (Box 203, Folder 21)
    - Then, 1972-73 (Box 204, Folder 1-7)
    - The Times, 1959 (Box 204, Folder 8-11)
    - The Tribal American, 1960 (Box 204, Folder 12-17)
    - Triple Solitaire, 1960s (Box 204, Folder 18-20)
    - Turnpike: A Novel of Momentum, 1978 (Box 205, Folder 1-4)
    - Undaunted by Odds, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - The United States Marines, 1956-57 (Box 205, Folder 6-14)
    - U.S.M.C., 1975 (Box 205, Folder 15-16)
    - W. Averill Harriman, 1985 (Box 205, Folder 17)
    - Walter Reuther, 1958-60 (Box 205, Folder 18-22)
    - Walter Reuther, 1958-60 (Box 206, Folder 1-18)
    - Walter Reuther, USIA, 1960 (Box 206, Folder 19-20)
    - The Water Machine, 1950s (Box 206, Folder 21)
    - When Churchill Walked Out on Himself, 1960s (Box 206, Folder 22)
    - Untitled poem, 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 207, Folder 2-3)
  - Writing fragments, undated (Box 207, Folder 4-6)
- Series II: Printed matter
  - Writings by Manchester
    - American Heritage (Box 207, Folder 7)
      - 'I Wish I'd Been There' - FDR Thunders, 1984 Dec
      - The Lion Caged, 1987 Feb-Mar
    - Apu (Box 207, Folder 8)
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Jan 21
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Jan 28
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Feb 4
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Feb 11
    - Apu (Box 207, Folder 9)
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Feb 18
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Feb 25
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Mar 4
    - Apu (Box 207, Folder 10)
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Mar 11
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Apr 1
      - Presidentin kuolema, 1967 Apr 8
    - The Atlantic Monthly (Box 207, Folder 11)
      - Douglas MacArthur and the Making of Modern Japan, 1978 Jul
    - Atlantida (Box 333)
      - La Muerts de un Presidente - primera parte, 1967 Feb
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica 15th ed. (Box 207, Folder 12)
      - Kennedy Family, 1974
      - Krupp Family, 1974
    - Epoca (Box 333)
      - Morte di un Presidente, 1967 Jan 15
      - Morte di un Presidente - seconda puntata, 1967 Jan 22
      - Morte di un Presidente - terza puntata, 1967 Jan 29
      - Morte di un Presidente - quarta puntata, 1967 Feb 5
      - Morte di un Presidente - quinta puntata, 1967 Feb 12
      - Morte di un Presidente - sesta puntata, 1967 Feb 19
      - Morte di un Presidente - settima puntata, 1967 Feb 26
      - Morte di un Presidente - ottava puntata, 1967 Mar 5
      - Vi Racconto la Storia Segreta del Mio Libro, 1967 Mar 26
      - I Kennedy Sparano a Zero, 1967 Apr 2
    - Esquire (Box 334)
      - In Defense of Snobs, 1962 Dec
      - Three Misspent Lives: William Manchester, 1968 Oct
    - Forbes (Box 207, Folder 13)
      - My Magnetometer Problem, 1995 Nov
    - Gardens, Houses and People (Box 207, Folder 14)
      - Private Life of H.L. Mencken, 1950 Nov
    - Good Housekeeping (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - An Act of Conscience, 1968 Nov
    - Harper's Magazine (Box 208, Folder 2)
      - Mencken and the Twenties, 1950 Jul
      - Mencken and The Mercury, 1950 Aug
    - Harper's Magazine (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - The Case of Luella Mundel, 1952 May
      - The Byrd Machine, 1952 Nov
      - Louisville Cashes in on Culture, 1955 Aug
      - Nelson Rockefeller's Moral Heritage, 1959 May
    - Holiday (Box 335)
      - Louiville, Belle of Kentucky, 1957 Jun
      - The United States Marines, 1957 Nov
      - Maryland's Historic Capital, 1958 Jun
      - The Rockefeller Family - Part I, 1958 Aug
      - The Rockefeller Family - Part II, 1958 Sep
      - The Rockefeller Family - Part III, 1958 Oct
      - The Rockefeller Family - Part IV, 1958 Nov
      - The Times: The World's Greatest Newspaper, 1959 Oct
    - Holiday (Box 336)
      - Walter Reuther - Part I, 1959 Nov
      - Walter Reuther - Part II, 1959 Dec
      - The Great Bank Holiday, 1960 Feb
      - Our War in the Pacific, 1960 Nov
    - Holiday (Box 337)
      - Murder Tour of New England, 1961 May
      - The Berkshire Hills, 1961 Aug
      - The Spanish-American War, 1961 Sep
      - The Department of the Treasury - Second of a Series, 1962 Feb
      - John F. Kennedy: Portrait of a President - Part One, 1962 Apr
    - Holiday (Box 338)
      - John F. Kennedy: Portrait of a President - Part Two, 1962 May
      - John F. Kennedy: Portrait of a President - Part Three, 1962 Jun
      - The Tribal American, 1962 Jul
      - The First World War, 1962 Nov
      - The Department of Defense - Tenth in a Series, 1963 May
      - Life Along the Connecticut, 1963 Jun
    - Holiday (Box 339)
      - Money, Bears & Bulls - A Look at Wall Street, 1964 Mar
      - The House of Krupp - Part I, 1964 Oct
      - The House of Krupp - Part II, 1964 Nov
      - The House of Krupp - Part III, 1964 Dec
      - The House of Krupp - Part IV, 1965 Jan
      - The House of Krupp - Part V, 1965 Feb
    - Holiday (Box 340)
      - The First World War, 1968 Nov
      - Our Men in Paris, 1969 Mar
    - Horizon (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - H.L. Mencken in Person, 1980 Sep
    - Humo (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Jan 21
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Jan 28
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Feb 4
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Feb 11
    - Humo (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Feb 18
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Feb 25
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Mar 4
    - Humo (Box 208, Folder 7)
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Mar 11
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Mar 18
      - De Dood van een President, 1967 Mar 25
    - The Illustrated London News (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - At Home With Churchill, 1987 May
    - Leadership South Africa (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Churchill at Home, 1987
      - Walking With Destiny, 1988
    - L'Express (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Les Krupp, 1970 Aug 10-16
      - Les Krupp (II), 1970 Aug 17-23
      - Les Krupp (III), 1970 Aug 24-30
      - Les Krupp (fin), 1970 Aug 31-Sep 6
    - The Literary Guild Magazine (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Inside the Third Reich: Memoirs by Albert Speer, 1970 Sep
    - Look (Box 340)
      - The Death of a President - Part I, 1967 Jan 24
      - The Death of a President - Part II, 1967 Feb 7
      - The Death of a President - Part III, 1967 Feb 21
      - The Death of a President - Part IV, 1967 Mar 7
      - William Manchester's Own Story, 1967 Apr 4
      - The Death of a President: The Book as Condensed in Four Installments in Look Magazine, 1967
      - Krupp, 1968 Aug 6
    - Manchete (Box 341)
      - A Morte de um Presidente, 1967 Jan 21
    - Modern Maturity (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Manchester on Leadership, 1988 Oct/Nov
    - The Nation (Box 209, Folder 6)
      - An Enemy of the People?, 1952 Aug 9
      - Bouquet for Mencken, 1953 Sep 12
    - National Review (Box 209, Folder 7)
      - Reflections on Egalitarianism, 1985 Mar 22
    - New York (Box 209, Folder 8)
      - Rock Bottom in America, 1974 Aug 5
    - The New York Times Magazine (Box 341)
      - Then, 1973 Nov 4
      - The Founding Grandfather, 1974 Oct 6
      - The Bloodiest Battle of All, 1987 Jun 14
      - The Biggest Con Man in the Marines, 1995 May 7
    - Our Times (Box 209, Folder 9)
      - Anatomy of a Novelist, 1960 Nov 9
      - John F. Kennedy: A Man Alone, 1962 Sep 19
    - Pan Am Clipper (Box 209, Folder 10)
      - The Last Lion: Winston Spencer Churchill Alone 1932-1940, 1989 Jun
    - Paris Match (Box 341)
      - Mort d'un President, 1967 Jan 14
      - Mort d'un President - II, 1967 Jan 21
      - Mort d'un President - III, 1967 Jan 28
    - The Pendleton Scout (Box 346)
      - United States Marine: For God, Country and Corps - He Remains Among the Elite, 1962 Nov 9
    - Private printing (Box 209, Folder 11)
      - The United States Marines [reprint], 1995?
    - Private printing (Box 209, Folder 12)
      - W. Averell Harriman (1891 - ), A Tribute, 1985 Nov 15
    - Reader's Digest (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Louisville Cashes in on Culture, 1955 Oct
      - All the News - And Then Some, 1959 Dec
    - Reader's Digest (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - American Caesar, 1979 Jul
    - Reader's Digest (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - A Day in the Life of Churchill, 1987 Oct
      - A Day in the Life of Churchill [Canadian edition], 1987 Nov
    - The Reporter (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Thirty-six Per Cent Interest - And 'No Questions Asked', 1954 Apr 13
      - The Life and Times of a Slum Landlord, 1956 Nov 15
    - The Saturday Evening Post (Box 342)
      - Record Run, 1957 Apr 13
    - Saturday Review (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - H. L. Mencken at Seventy-five, 1955 Sep 10 Nov
    - The Shukan Shincho (Box 210, Folder 6)
      - [The Death of a President,], 1967 Jan 28
      - [The Death of a President,], 1967 Feb 4
    - The Shukan Shincho (Box 210, Folder 7)
      - [The Death of a President,], 1967 Feb 11
      - [The Death of a President,], 1967 Feb 18
    - Sky (Box 210, Folder 8)
      - The Treasury: Inside the Nation's Vaults, 1976 Sep
    - Sondags - B.T. (Box 342)
      - En praesidents dod, 1967 Feb 3
      - En praesidents dod...2, 1967 Feb 10
      - En praesidents dod...3, 1967 Feb 17
      - En praesidents dod...4, 1967 Feb 24
      - En praesidents dod...5, 1967 Mar 3
      - En praesidents dod...7, 1967 Mar 17
      - En praesidents dod...8, 1967 Mar 24
      - En praesidents dod...sidste afsnit, 1967 Apr 7
    - Stern (Box 343)
      - Der Tod des Prasidenten, 1967 Jan 15
      - Der Tod des Prasidenten, 1967 Jan 22
      - Der Tod des Prasidenten, 1967 Jan 29
      - Der Tod des Prasidenten, 1967 Feb 5
      - Der Tod des Prasidenten, 1967 Feb 12
      - Der Tod des Prasidenten, 1967 Feb 19
      - Der Tod des Prasidenten, 1967 Feb 26
      - Der Tod des Prasidenten, 1967 Mar 5
      - Was hatten die Kennedys denn zu verbergen?, 1967 Mar 26
    - The Sunday Times Magazine (Box 344)
      - The America that Died at Dallas, 1973 Nov 18
    - U.S. News (Box 210, Folder 9)
      - A World Lit Only By Change, 1993 Oct 25
    - Vecko (Box 344)
      - Presidentens Dod, 1967 Jan 11
      - Presidentens Dod, 1967 Feb 15
      - Presidentens Dod, 1967 Mar 1
    - Vikan (Box 344)
      - Daudi Forseta, 1967 Feb 23
      - Daudi Forseta 2. hluti, 1967 Mar 2
      - Daudi Forseta 3. hluti, 1967 Mar 9
      - Daudi Forseta 8. hluti, 1967 Apr 13
      - Daudi Forseta, skrifar um, 1967 Apr 27
      - Barattan um Bokina, 1967 May 3
    - Wesleyan Alumnus (Box 210, Folder 10)
      - Anatomy of a Novelist, 1960 Aug
    - Newspapers: serializations and clippings (Box 345, Folder 1)
      - Baltimore Sun, 1950s
    - Newspapers: serializations and clippings (Box 345, Folder 2)
      - Assorted other clippings, 1953-1992
    - Newspapers: serializations and clippings (Box 345, Folder 3)
      - The Death of a President, Greek serialization, 1967
    - Newspaper serializations (Box 346)
      - The Death of a President, 1967
      - Krupp, parts I-V, 1969
  - Serials
    - American Heritage, 1982 Feb/Mar (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - American Heritage, 1982 Jun/Jul (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - The Atlantic, 1967 May (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - The Atlantic, 1968 Dec (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Book & Author, 1983 Jan/Feb (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Book Digest, 1975 Mar (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Book Digest, 1978 Dec (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club News, 1951 Jan (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club News, 1967 April (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club News, 1980 Sep (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club News, 1983 Jun (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Bullough, Vern L., The Rockefellers and Sex Research, The Journal of Sex Research, 1985 May, 1978 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Churchillbooks, 1990-91 (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Cross & Crescent, 1981 May (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Current Biography, 1967 Nov (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - The Economist, 1969 May 10 (Box 211, Folder 16)
    - Esquire, 1965 Apr (Box 347)
    - Esquire, 1967 Jun (Box 347)
    - Evergreen Review, 1967 Aug (Box 211, Folder 17)
    - Fatos Fotos, 1966 Dec 31 (Box 347)
    - Fatos Fotos, 1967 Feb 18 (Box 347)
    - Finest Hour, 1983 Summer-1988 Spring (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Finest Hour, 1988 Summer-1990 4th qtr. (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Finest Hour, 1991 1st qtr.-1993 2nd qtr. (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Finest Hour, 1993 3rd qtr.-1995-96 Winter (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Finest Hour, 1996 Spring-1998 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Follow Me, 1994 Jan-Feb (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Fortune, 1961 Mar (Box 347)
    - Gardens, Houses and People, 1951 Jan (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - The Hastings Center Report, 1972 Sep (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - The Hollins Critic, 1971 Aug (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Humanities, 2002 May/Jun (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - ICS Stores Catalogue, 1994 Winter/Spring (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - LG, 1974 Dec (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Literama, 1978 May (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - The Literary Guild Magazine, 1968 Dec (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Life, 1937 Jun 7 (Box 347)
    - Life, 1963 Dec 6 (Box 347)
    - Life, John F. Kennedy Memorial Edition, 1963 (Box 347)
    - Life, 1969 Jan 10 (Box 347)
    - Life, 1971 Dec 31 (Box 347)
    - Look, 1964 Nov 17 (Box 348)
    - Look JFK Memorial Book, 1964 (Box 348)
    - Look, 1967 Jan 10 (Box 348)
    - Manchete, 1967 Jan 7 (Box 348)
    - Massachusetts Alumnus, 1962 Summer (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts Alumnus, 1965 Summer (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Menckeniana, 1962 Summer (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Menckeniana, 1968 Fall (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Mill Mountain Review, 1971 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Motion Picture, 1967 May (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - The New Republic, 1969 Apr 26 (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - New York, 1972 Feb 14 (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1967 Apr (Box 348)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1967 Jun 4 (Box 348)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1967 Aug 13 (Box 348)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1969 Apr 13 (Box 348)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1976 Aug 1 (Box 348)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1988 Nov 20 (Box 348)
    - The New Yorker, 1951 Jan 20 (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - The New Yorker, 1961 Dec 23 (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - The New Yorker, 1993 Oct 4 (Box 213, Folder 12-13)
    - Newsweek, 1966 Sep 5 (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - Newsweek, 1966 Oct 3 (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - Newsweek, 1966 Dec 26 (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - Newsweek, 1983 May 9 (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - Newsweek, 1994 May 30 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Northeast, 1984 Apr 22 (Box 349)
    - Northeast, 1986 May 18 (Box 349)
    - Our Times, 1965 Nov 8 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Parr, Albert Eide, article reprints, 1967-73 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - People, 1978 Nov 27 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Photoplay, 1966 Apr (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Publishers Weekly, 1974 Sep 2 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Publishers Weekly, 1978 Apr 24 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Punch, 1967 Apr 19 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Read, 1965 Nov 15 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Red & Black, 1985 May (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Saturday Review, 1967 Apr 15 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Speaking of Holiday, 1959 Jul (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Stern, 1967 Mar 12 (Box 349)
    - Stern, 1967 Mar 19 (Box 349)
    - Stern, 1967 Apr 2 (Box 349)
    - Stern, 1967 Mai 7 (Box 349)
    - Sun Magazine, 1980 Sep 7 (Box 349)
    - The Sunday Times Magazine, 1966 Oct 9 (Box 349)
    - Time, 1951 Jan 8 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - Time, 1967 Apr 7 (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - Time, 1968 Sep 6 (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - Time, 1968 Dec 20 (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - Time, 1983 May 9 (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - Time, 1994 May 30 (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - U.S. Catholic, 1967 May (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - U.S. News & World Report, 1994 May 30 (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Vecko Revyn, 1967 Nov 11 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - The Washington Post Magazine, 1995 May 7 (Box 214, Folder 22)
    - The Wesleyan Alumnus, 1965 Aug (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - Word Study, 1960 Dec (Box 214, Folder 24)
    - The Yale Review, 1958 Autumn (Box 214, Folder 25)
  - Newspapers